Kelli Uyeda

<u>KELLIKELLS@GMAIL.COM</u> | (626) 641-2379 | South Pasadena, CA

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kelli-uyeda | Github: https://kellikells.github.io/profileKelli

Web Developer

College graduate with a bachelor's degree in English, and more recently completed UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp. Leveraging a background in hospitality to build a more intuitive user experience on the web. Known for the abilities to problem solve and be a successful team player, strengths are also in meeting deadlines, creativity, and teamwork.

Representative Projects & Results:

Iphy Weather: Primarily worked on back-end development to create a web application that provides the user with weather information based on user requests. Added user's ability to search weather conditions by *zipcode* through pulling data from a weather API. Successfully completed the project working with a team of 4 members in 12 days.

Five Star Foodies: Worked on both front-end development using React, and back-end programming to produce a web application that provides users with restaurant information. Assisted with formatting page layout and worked with another team member to incorporate Auth0 to authenticate and authorize users.

Education

University of California Los Angeles Extension - **Coding Bootcamp**University of California Los Angeles - **Bachelor of Arts in English**

Technology Summary

Browser Based: React.js; HTML5; ES6 JavaScript; jQuery; Bootstrap; Responsive Design; Tailwind CSS; XML, CSS3

Jinja; JSX; Handlebars

Web framework: Django, Flask

Server Side Development: Node.js; Express; MERN Stack; AJAX

Programming: Python; Java **Deployment:** AWS; Heroku; Git

Databases: MongoDB; MySQL; Firebase

Windows; Mac

Work Experience

Server2018-2019My Ramen BarLos Angeles, CA

Lead Server	2018-2019
Dan Modern Chinese Restaurant	Pasadena, CA
Lead Server	2014-2018
Gyu Kaku Japanese BBQ	Pasadena, CA